icobench.com 2018-07-03

# 

         PRIVACY POLICY
THIS PRIVACY POLICY WAS LAST UPDATED ON 25TH OF MAY, 2018.
THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS INCORPORATED AND MADE A PART OF ICOBENCH
TERMS OF SERVICE. ICOBENCH HAS CREATED THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT IN
ORDER TO DISCLOSE OUR INFORMATION GATHERING AND DISSEMINATION
PRACTICES FOR ICOBENCH WEBSITE. PLEASE READ THIS DOCUMENT
CAREFULLY. IT CONTAINS IMPORTANT INFORMATION THAT YOU SHOULD
KNOW BEFORE CONTINUING TO USE OUR WEBSITE OR SERVICES (AS SUCH
TERM DEFINED IN THE TERMS OF SERVICES). BY CONTINUING TO USE
ICOBENCH WEBSITE AND SERVICES YOU WILL BE DEEMED TO HAVE
ACCEPTED THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
INTRODUCTION
1.     This Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred to as the “Policy”) sets forth the
general rules of collection, processing, distribution, use and storage of Website user’s
Personal data including any dispute concerning privacy under current General Data
Protection Regulation (GDPR), and in accordance with the data protection
regulations applicable to the ICObench (hereinafter the “ICObench”, “Company”, “Us”,
“We”).
2.     It is understood and presumed that by the fact of use of the Website and its
services or by clicking ““REGISTER” button the User gives Consent, that he/she/it
has fully read, understood and accepted this Policy. If any User does not agree with
this Policy in general or any part of it, such User should withhold from using the
Website and its services.
DEFINITIONS
3.     The following definitions and rules of interpretation apply in this Privacy policy:
a)     Personal data
Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural
person (“data subject”). An identifiable natural person is an individual that can be
identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name,
an identification number, address or other identification data.
b)     Data subject
Data subject is any identified or identifiable natural person, whose personal data is
processed by the controller responsible for the processing.

c)     Processing
Processing is any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or
on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection,
recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval,
consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making
available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.
d)     Restriction of processing
Restriction of processing is the marking of stored personal data with the aim of limiting
their processing in the future.
e)     Profiling
Profiling means any form of automated processing of personal data consisting of the
use of personal data to evaluate certain personal aspects relating to a natural person,
in particular to analyse or predict aspects concerning that natural person's performance
at work, economic situation, health, personal preferences, interests, reliability,
behaviour, location or movements.
f)Pseudonymisation
Pseudonymisation is the processing of personal data in such a manner that the
personal data can no longer be attributed to a specific data subject without the use of
additional information, provided that such additional information is kept separately and
is subject to technical and organisational measures to ensure that the personal data are
not attributed to an identified or identifiable natural person.
g)     Controller or controller responsible for the processing
Controller or controller responsible for the processing is the natural or legal person,
public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines
the purposes and means of the processing of personal data; where the purposes and
means of such processing are determined by Curaçaon legislation.
h)     Processor
Processor is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which
processes personal data on behalf of the controller.
i) Recipient
Recipient is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or another body, to which
the personal data are disclosed, whether a third party or not. However, public
authorities which may receive personal data in the framework of a particular inquiry in
accordance with Union or Member State law shall not be regarded as recipients; the
processing of those data by those public authorities shall be in compliance with the
applicable data protection rules according to the purposes of the processing.

j) Third party
Third party is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or body other than the
data subject, controller, processor and persons who, under the direct authority of the
controller or processor, are authorized to process personal data.
k)     Consent
Consent of the data subject is any freely given, specific, informed and unambiguous
indication of the data subject's wishes by which he or she, by a statement or by a clear
affirmative action, signifies agreement to the processing of personal data relating to him
or her.
l) Website
A group of interrelated websites owned and operated by ICObench, available in the
Internet via address: icobench.com.
m)     Cookies
A cookie is a text file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is
sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is
then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.
   Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie
will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless
deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will
expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.Cookies do not
typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal
information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and
obtained from cookies. For more information on managing cookies, please go to
www.allaboutcookies.org, or visit www.youronlinechoices.com.
n)     Sensitive personal information
An information about an individual that reveals their racial or ethnic origin, political
opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, genetic
information, biometric information for the purpose of uniquely identifying an individual,
information concerning health or information concerning a natural person’s sex life or
sexual orientation. ICObench does not collect or store such information.
MODIFICATIONS
4.     This Privacy Policy may be modified, changed, supplemented, updated at any
time with prior written notice from ICObench. Your continued use of the Website and
its services after any amendments or alterations of this Privacy Policy without

notification of ICObench shall constitute your consent hereto and acceptance hereof
of an updated version of this Privacy Policy. At any case, the date of the most recent
amendments and alterations will be indicated at the top of this web page. If the User
does not agree to such revised terms of the Privacy Policy or Terms of Use he/she/it
must stop using this Website and hia account and may withdraw from his/her/its
obligations under this Privacy Policy.
INFORMATION ABOUT THE DATA CONTROLLER
5.     The data controller of this Website is ICObench. Contact details can be
received at:: info@icobench.com or via https://icobench.com/contact.
LEGAL BASIS FOR THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA
All personal data of data subject is processed with aim of compliance with a legal
obligation under Art. 6(1) lit. of GDPR under which data controller is obliged to
receive consent of data subject for specific processing operations with personal data.
COLLECTION OF PERSONAL DATA AND INFORMATION
6.     The Website of the ICObench collects a series of general data and information
when a data subject or automated system calls up the website. This general data and
information are stored in the server log files.
7.     The following information may be collected for general purposes:
(1) the browser type and its version;
(2) the operating system used by the accessing system,
(3) the website from which an accessing system reaches the website;
(4) the sub-websites;
(5) the date and time of access to the Internet site;
(6) an Internet protocol address (IP address);
(7) the Internet service provider of the accessing system; and
(8) any other similar data and information that may be used in the event of attacks on
our information technology systems.
8.     When using these general data and information, the ICObench does not draw
any conclusions about the data subject. Rather, this information is needed to (1)
deliver the content of our website correctly, (2) optimize the content of our website as
well as its advertisement, (3) ensure the long-term viability of our information

           technology systems and website technology, and (4) provide law enforcement
           authorities with the information necessary for criminal prosecution in case of a
           cyber-attack. Therefore, the ICObench analyzes anonymously collected data and
           information statistically, with the aim of increasing the data protection and data
           security of our enterprise, and to ensure an optimal level of protection for the personal
           data we process. The anonymous data of the server log files are stored separately
           from all personal data provided by a data subject.
           9.    The following information can be collected for services purposes:
           (1) Contact information, such as name, home address, and email address;
           (2) Account information, such as username and password;
           (3) Information related to you virtual wallets public addresses;
           (4) Financial information, such as bank account numbers, bank statement, and
           trading information;
           (5) Identity verification information, such as images of your government issued ID,
           passport, national ID card, or driving license.
           (6) Residence verification information, such as Utility bill details or similar
           information.
           COOKIES POLICY
           10.   The internet pages of this Website use cookies for the following purposes:
   Purpose                                Description                             Type & Expiry
                        Our web sites are built using common internet
Performance           platforms. These have built-in cookies which help               Session
 (i.e., User's    compatibility issues (e.g., to identify your browser type)  Deleted upon closing
   Browser)          and improve performance (e.g., quicker loading of              the browser
                                            content).
                      If you register for access to a restricted area, our
Security (e.g.                                                                        Session
                      cookies ensure that your device is logged for the
  Asp .NET)                                                                   Deleted upon closing
                  duration of your visit. You will need your username and
    Cookies                                                                         the browser
                           password to access the restricted areas.
                   Our cookies may also remember your site preferences
                    (e.g., language) or seek to enhance your experience               Session
      Site
                   (e.g., by personalizing a greeting or content). This will  Deleted upon closing
Preferences
                   apply to areas where you have registered specifically            the browser
                               for access or create an account.
                     We use several third party analytics tools to help us      Persistent, but will
  Analytical
                     understand how site visitors use our web site. This       delete automatically

                allows us to improve the quality and content on Website        after two years if you
                  for our visitors. The aggregated statistical data cover          no longer visit
                items such as total visits or page views, and referrers to            Website.
                                         our web sites.
                 We use a third party survey tool to invite a percentage
                                                                                     1 Session
                 of visitors to provide their feedback. Cookies are used
                                                                               Deleted upon closing
                   to prevent visitors from being invited multiple times.
                                                                                    the browser
                  The first cookie (1) is set if the visitor is not invited to
Site visitor     participate in the survey, and is used to ensure visitors
                                                                                    2 Persistent
feedback                  are not invited after their first page view.
                                                                               Deleted automatically
                   The second cookie (2) is set if the visitor is invited to
                                                                                  after 90 days or
                    participate in the survey, and is used to ensure the
                                                                                presenting survey
                  visitor is not invited again to participate for a period of
                                                                                        invite.
                                           90 days.
                  We use third party social media widgets or buttons to
                     provide you with additional functionality to share
                  content from our web pages to social media websites
                and email. Use of these widgets or buttons may place a         Persistent, but will be
                  cookie on your device to make their service easier to        deleted automatically
  Social
                     use, ensure your interaction is displayed on our          after two years if you
 sharing
                      webpages (e.g. the social share count cache is               no longer visit
                    updated) and log information about your activities                Website.
                       across the Internet and on our web sites. We
                     encourage you to review each provider's privacy
                        information before using any such service.
         11. The data subject may, as stated above, prevent the setting of cookies through our
         website at any time by means of a corresponding adjustment of the web browser used
         and thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. For example, most browsers allow
         you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary
         from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain
         up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:
         (1)   https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en (Chrome);
         (2)   https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-prefere
         nces (Firefox);
         (3)   http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/ (Opera);
         (4)   https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-
         manage-cookies (Internet Explorer);
         (5)   https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411 (Safari); and
         (6)   https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy
         (Edge).
         12. You also have act in the following ways:
         (1)   Opting-Out
         As part of our commitment to fair information practices, ICObench allow you to opt
         out of the use of information about your activities on other websites to provide you
         with Interest-based advertising. You can opt out of Google Analytics by installing
         Google’s opt-out browser add-on, and out of interest-based Google ads

using Google’s Ads Settings. Even if you opt out, you may still receive ICObench
advertising. It just means that the advertising you see will not be customised for you.
(2)   Refusing Cookies
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising
when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.You can limit the
collection of your information by disabling cookies on your browser. You may also
be able to modify your browser settings to require your permission each time a site
attempts to set a cookie. However, our website(s) (and many other websites) rely on
cookies to enable certain functionality. If you choose to disable cookies, some of the
services available on our website may not work properly.
(3)   Non-ICObench Websites and Links
Our websites may contain links to non-ICObench websites. We are not responsible
for the practices of those third party websites. Where you access other websites
from our sites using the links provided, the operators of these websites may use
cookies in accordance with their own cookies policy, which may differ from ours.
You should read their privacy and cookie policies carefully before you provide any
personal information to them.
(4)   Caution regarding automatic Cookie Functionality
Browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer allow you to store passwords and
logon IDs so you do not need to re-enter this information each time you access a
web site. ICObench strongly urges you NOT to use this functionality to prevent
unauthorized use of your online banking access code(s). This Personal Data
includes:
13. The user is notified that blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the
usability of many websites. If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all or certain
features on our website.
INFORMATION COLLECTED BY REGISTRATION ON THE WEBSITE
14.   The data subject has the possibility to register on the website of the controller
with the indication of personal data. Which personal data are transmitted to the
controller is determined by the respective input mask used for the registration. The
personal data entered by the data subject is collected and stored exclusively for
internal use by the controller, and for his own purposes. The controller may request
transfer to one or more processors (e.g. a parcel service) that also uses personal
data for an internal purpose which is attributable to the controller.

15.    By registering on the website of the controller, the IP address—assigned by the
Internet service provider (ISP) and used by the data subject—date, and time of the
registration are also stored. The storage of this data takes place against the
background that this is the only way to prevent the misuse of our services, and, if
necessary, to make it possible to investigate committed offenses. Insofar, the storage
of this data is necessary to secure the controller. This data is not passed on to third
parties unless there is a statutory obligation to pass on the data, or if the transfer
serves the aim of criminal prosecution.
16.    The registration of the data subject, with the voluntary indication of personal
data, is intended to enable the controller to offer the data subject contents or services
that may only be offered to registered users due to the nature of the matter in
question. Registered persons are free to change the personal data specified during
the registration at any time, or to have them completely deleted from the data stock of
the controller.
INFORMATION COLLECTED BY SUBSCRIPTION TO OUR NEWSLETTERS
17.    On the website of the ICObench, users are given the opportunity to subscribe
to newsletter service. The input mask used for this purpose determines what personal
data are transmitted, as well as when the newsletter is ordered from the controller.
The newsletter may only be received by the data subject if (1) the data subject has a
valid e-mail address and (2) the data subject registers for the newsletter shipping. A
confirmation e-mail will be sent to the e-mail address registered by a data subject for
the first time for newsletter shipping, for legal reasons, in the double opt-in procedure.
This confirmation e-mail is used to prove whether the owner of the e-mail address as
the data subject is authorized to receive the newsletter. During the registration for the
newsletter, an Website also store an IP address of the computer system assigned by
the Internet service provider (ISP) and used by the data subject at the time of the
registration, as well as the date and time of the registration. The personal data
collected as part of a registration for the newsletter will only be used to send our
newsletter.
INFORMATION COLLECTED BY CONTACTING US VIA THE WEBSITE
18.    The website contains information that enables a quick electronic contact to
ICObench. If a data subject contacts the controller by e-mail or via a contact form, the
personal data transmitted by the data subject is automatically stored. Such personal
data transmitted on a voluntary basis by a data subject to the data controller is stored

for the purpose of processing or contacting the data subject. There is no transfer of
this personal data to third parties.
ERASURE AND BLOCK OF PERSONAL DATA
19.     The data controller process and store the personal data of the data subject only
for the period necessary to achieve the purpose of storage. If the storage purpose is
not applicable, or if a storage period expires, the personal data is routinely blocked or
erased.
RIGHTS OF THE DATA SUBJECT
20.     Subject to certain limitations on certain rights, you have the following rights in
relation to your information, which you can exercise by contacting ICObench, DPO or
sending an email to info@icobench.com:
(1) to request access to your information and information related to our use and
processing of your information, including:
a)      the purposes of the processing;
b)      the categories of personal data concerned;
c)      the recipients or categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been
or will be disclosed, in particular recipients in third countries or international
organisations;
d)      where possible, the envisaged period for which the personal data will be stored,
or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine that period;
e)      the existence of the right to request from the controller rectification or erasure of
personal data, or restriction of processing of personal data concerning the data
subject, or to object to such processing;
f) the existence of the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority;
g)      where the personal data are not collected from the data subject, any available
information as to their source;
h)      the existence of automated decision-making, including profiling, referred to in
Article 22(1) and (4) of the GDPR and, at least in those cases, meaningful information
about the logic involved, as well as the significance and envisaged consequences of
such processing for the data subject.
i) to obtain information as to whether personal data are transferred to a third country
or to an international organisation. Where this is the case, the data subject shall have
the right to be informed of the appropriate safeguards relating to the transfer.

(2) To request and to obtain from the controller the confirmation as to whether or not
personal data concerning him/her/it is being processed.
(3) to request the correction or deletion of your information. Data subject can request
to delete his personal information (the right to be forgotten) in case:
a)     the personal data is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it
was collected or otherwise processed.
b)     the data subject withdraws consent to which the processing is based according
to point (a) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR, or point (a) of Article 9(2) of the GDPR, and
where there is no other legal ground for the processing.
c)     the data subject objects to the processing pursuant to Article 21(1) of the
GDPR and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing, or the data
subject objects to the processing pursuant to Article 21(2) of the GDPR.
d)     the personal data have been unlawfully processed.
e)     the personal data must be erased for compliance with a legal obligation in
Curaçao.
f) the personal data have been collected in relation to the offer of information society
services referred to in Article 8(1) of the GDPR.
If one of the aforementioned reasons applies, and a data subject wishes to request
the erasure of personal data stored by the ICObench, he or she may, at any time,
contact any employee of the controller. An employee of ICObench shall promptly
ensure that the erasure request is complied with immediately.
(4) to request that company restrict the processing of your information in cases
when:
a)     the accuracy of the personal data is contested by the data subject, for a period
enabling the controller to verify the accuracy of the personal data.
b)     the processing is unlawful and the data subject opposes the erasure of the
personal data and requests instead the restriction of their use instead.
c)     the controller no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of the
processing, but they are required by the data subject for the establishment, exercise
or defence of legal claims.
d)     the data subject has objected to processing pursuant to Article 21(1) of the
GDPR pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of the controller
override those of the data subject.
If one of the aforementioned conditions is met, and a data subject wishes to request
the restriction of the processing of personal data stored by the ICObench, he or she

may at any time contact any employee of the controller. The employee of the
ICObench will arrange the restriction of the processing.
(5) to receive information which data subject have provided to us in a structured,
commonly used and machine-readable format and the right to have that information
transferred to another data controller (including a third party data controller);
(6) to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes; and
(7) to withdraw your data protection consent to our use of your information at any
time where data controller rely on your consent to use or process that information.
21.    In accordance with Article 77 of the General Data Protection Regulation, data
subject have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in
the Member State of his/her/its habitual residence, place of work or of an alleged
infringement of the General Data Protection Regulation.
DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION
22.    We may disclose any information we collect about you, whether you are a
current or former customer, including nonpublic personal information and any other
information we collect, to ICObench affiliated companies and to non-affiliated third
parties, which include non-financial companies, such as email service providers and
fraud verification services, and others, such as other ICObench users with which you
engage in transactions. We may make such disclosures:
(1) to service providers that perform marketing services on our behalf; and
(2) for everyday business purposes, such as to process transactions, maintain
accounts, respond to court orders and legal investigations or report to credit bureaus.
(3) if we are under a duty to disclose or share your information to comply with our
legal obligations.
23.    Other than in connection with a merger, sale of ICObench assets, financing or
acquisition, we will not sell or rent any of your information to third parties for their own
marketing purposes.
24.    Please note that third parties that support our customer identification and
anti-fraud controls may retain and use information about you to perform services on
our behalf and to improve their services. By using our Services, you consent to the
retention and use of such information by these providers to improve their services.
25.    We may also share aggregated or de-identified information with our affiliated
companies or non-affiliated third parties, which cannot reasonably be used to identify
you.

26.     We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties and legal and
regulatory authorities, and transfer your Personal Information outside the EEA. It may
be processed by a staff member operating outside the EEA who work for us or for
one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in amongst other things, the
fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of
support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing
or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is
treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
27.     Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely
secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot
guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site, and any transmission is at
your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures
and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.
28.      We will also transfer your information outside the EEA or to an international
organisation in the unlikely event that we are required to comply with legal obligations
to which we are subject (compliance with a court order, for example). Where we are
required to do so, we will ensure appropriate safeguards and protections are in place.
CHILDREN‘S PRIVACY
29.     The Website and any products or Services available on Website are not
intended to solicit information of any kind from persons under 18 years of age.
EXISTENCE OF AUTOMATED DECISION-MAKING
30.     Data controller does not use automatic decision-making or profiling to process
and use data subject’s personal data.
SECURITY
31.     ICObench use relevant electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the
privacy of the information the User provide to ICObench from loss, misuse, disclosure,
alteration and destruction. Please note that transmission of data or information
(including communications by e-mail) over the Internet or other publicly accessible
networks is not one hundred percent secure. Please note that ICObench are not
liable for the security of any data Users are transmitting over the Internet, or third
party content.

PRIVACY-RELATED INQUIRIES AND COMPLAINTS NOTICE
32.    ICObench takes and addresses its users' privacy concerns with utmost respect
and attention. If you believe that there was an instance of non-compliance with this
Privacy Policy with regard to your personal information or you have other related
inquiries  or   concerns,    you   may    write  or  contact   ICObench      at  email:
info@icobench.com. In your message, please describe in as much detail as possible
the nature of your inquiry or the ways in which you believe that the Privacy Policy has
not been complied with. We will investigate your inquiry or complaint promptly.
Please note that if you provide ICObench with inconsistent privacy preferences,
ICObench cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be
honored.
